[ED.
Good morning.
I'm in the biggest hurry of the youtube season so far.
I'm in Osaka today for the live broadcast of "Justice on the side of Justice" from 9:30am.
But the bullet train was stopped because of the typhoon.
Yesterday.
I waited for 2 hours and a half to get to the U.S., and finally flew back to the U.S. on the first plane in the morning, and now I'm here, and it's only 7 minutes to the first flight.
I've only got 7 minutes until the first meeting and 30 minutes until I get off the plane, but everyone is still here, and I can only do my base makeup, and I haven't even finished my base makeup yet.
At any rate, I have to hurry somehow.
I'll do my best!
I'll do my best! And after that, there will be a special feature!
I'll do my best! Oh no, I'm in a hurry!
We're done with the maintenance routine.
We've moved on, rehearsal in an hour, rehearsal in 50 minutes, so first of all, I'm eating my lunch!
Awesome, I almost ate a frozen flavored hamburger and ramen!
Hamburgers and scallops something, something...
But...
I'm already thinking about what I'm going to eat at the airport on the way home while I'm eating this.
What?
Maybe the fans won't make it to Osaka.
They might come and it'll be over.
That's too bad.
I really don't want to give it to them.
It hurts my heart. It really does.
People are always saying on TV that it's just a piece of bread.
They've worked their whole lives to get here to Osaka, and now it's over.
It's just too bad.
It's already a beautiful day.
It's so sunny after a typhoon.
They call it less than a typhoon.
It's going to start soon.
They made me pretty!
The outfit is like this.
I left the hair to her, and this is what she looked like.
The back is cute, too.
It's so cute!Awesome and cute.
I opened it.
Two hours of tokes with this one.
First of all...
I don't feel like I can do it well at all.
There is so much to think about and do!
I have more than a concert to do
I'll do my best.
What are you going to eat at the airport?
Takoyaki.
Yes.
Udon noodles?
I'd really like to eat udon.
I'm looking forward to it.
I'll do my best!
Hello, it's 5:30 in the evening today.
Today I'm recording a show called "out of 48." I'm the MC for an AKB audition show, so we're filming two shows.
I slept until 4 am.
What's that? I woke up at about 8, drank some water, and then I've been on my cell phone almost the whole time.
Lam was at 4:00.
How can you sleep so long?
So I feel like I just woke up.
It's 5:30 in the evening.
That's great.
Why are you there?
Two done.
You've slept through the night.
I have time today.
Your clothes are cute. I'm thinking of getting myself one of these.
Cute clothes.
Yes, ma'am.
I'm moving on.
Let's go for it.
Thank you for your hard work.
We've just finished two recordings.
I'm really looking forward to this out of the recordings.I'm really looking forward to this "out of" recording!
A lot.
That's great.
You've only been active for five hours.
It's not because I sleep too much.
It's just that every so often I go home, sleep another three hours, wake up at 1:00, and don't get up until the morning.
Thank you for your time.
Hello. - Hello.
Good afternoon.
I'm playing a regular role today.
I don't know why Yoo-kun is so much better than me.
I ate a candy bar and brushed my teeth.
Yeah, I know.
Maybe I'll show you how I brush my teeth for the first time.
That's right.
We're gonna brush our teeth and do those back muscles.
And we're gonna floss.
First, you brush your teeth, and then you floss.
It's called plaque.
It's about 60% plaque.
That's what happens.
If you leave it alone for a few days...
It turns into something like tartar.
and you have to go to the dentist.
So if you brush your teeth and floss, you can get the plaque between your teeth.
I'm brushing my teeth now.
I'm brushing my teeth right now.
I'm brushing my teeth.
I'm not brushing all the way down.
I'm not brushing the right side.
Don't tell me.
I'll give you three.
And now this... floss.
It's a Y-shaped floss from Clinica.
Isn't it cute that it comes in three different colors?
I'm gonna use the blue one in the front.I'll use the blue one in the front.
I have to do it.
I don't know, I just feel like I have to do it.
First of all, it's so easy to hold.
It's so easy!
It goes all the way to the back.
And my mom uses it, too.
I saw it on a cup when I went home.
This is so good.
I wasn't sure if I should show you how cute she is.
Can we not do this yet?
I just...
I wasn't sure if I could make you look pretty.
I don't know.
I've been thinking about whitening.
I've been thinking about the color.
But I think it's more important to have healthy teeth.
It's more important.
That's one of the things.
In AKB, you interact with fans
You get to interact with fans and talk to them up close.
You know...
You get a lot of attention in your hometown.
They look at you more than you think.
So I thought I'd be a little more careful.
I started doing this.
I'm going to sleep by doing this.
I feel like I can sleep.
I feel like if I don't do it, I get all misty.
So I'm like, "Okay, I'm gonna do the toothbrush.
I'm going to cross my teeth and clean my mouth.
It's really important to have a clean mouth.
I know it sounds like an adage, but...
But I'm sure you're curious about this.
Let me introduce you to it like a commercial.
This way!This way!
Ta-da!
YG Floss by Clinica
They also have this pouch type.
This one has a zipper too, so it's really nice!
I'll tell you the details of this product and
And also, we are running a campaign right now.
I've also included the details in the summary section of the video.
So please check it out!
Shall we go and shoot a YouTube video?
Yes, that's right.
I'm going to let my hair down a little bit.
Let's take it down and get dressed.
YouFizz...
There we go.
I'm going to go film for YouTube.
I'll do my best!
So how was it?
Well, I spent a few days on the set this time.
Mr. S. and I had some shots taken.
Well, it was a typical work scene for the past few days.
Yes, after this, I'm going to shoot a YouTube video.
I would like to go out to dinner with Mr. S today.
That's all for now, Yukirinukoto and Kajiwan Yuki!
See you soon!
I was actually going to do a project to press the "like" button on every good comment.
I was going to press "like" on everyone's comments, but there were too many comments I wanted to press "ba-ba-ba" on before I could press "like" on the comments I wanted to press "like" on.
I always read all the comments, so basically, as soon as I feel like I'm going to like something, I just take a quick snapshot of it and then I open up my list folder and it just accumulates.
I opened up my list folder and accumulated about 10 comments.
I'm going to release them, and today, today, I'm going to take a video of it.
I'm going to take a video of it today. I'm like, "Ugh!
Why are you saying this? But by talking about it here in the video.
By talking about it here in the video, it will be digested.
I'd like to make a video of the comment patrol today.